{"data":[{"question":"The Bakers ________ lunch","a":"having","b":"is having","c":"are having","d":"has","answer":"3","explain":"Very good! Correct \n- Present continuous \n-The Bakers is plural","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"I don't have ________ money","a":"much","b":"many","c":"no","d":"a few","answer":"1","explain":"Very good! Correct \n- Many\/ a few + countable noun \n- Much + uncountable \n- No: is not suitable because we have used \"don't\"","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"________ is the best football team in our school.","a":"Our","b":"Ours","c":"We","d":"Our's","answer":"2","explain":"- Ours: used as a possessive pronoun followed by a verb (ours = our football)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"Many retirees feel useless because they ________.","a":"do volunteer work","b":"have limited incomes","c":"aren't working","d":"can't help themselves","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present continuous.\u00a0\n- Retire- not working anymore- feel useless.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"It's very painful! ________ I've worked for a long time in my garden, the woman said.","a":"because","b":"for","c":"by","d":"as soon as","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Because + clause: used when you are giving the reason for something.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The woman has hurt her back ________ for too long.","a":"to bend","b":"by bending","c":"for bending","d":"owing to you bend","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Someone gets hurt by something\/someone.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"A lot of passengers who ________ in the ship crash are still suffering from shock.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Simple past tense: express the idea that an action started and finished in the past.\u00a0\n- Subject (A lot of passengers) is plural.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"\"How many ships ________ there in our merchant fleet?\" Mr.Pike asked me.","a":"had been","b":"have been","c":"had been","d":"are","answer":"4","explain":"\n- How many + countable nouns + are there....?","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"I ________ in this garage as a car mechanic for 15 years.","a":"has been working","b":"have been working","c":"had worked","d":"worked","answer":"2","explain":"\n- We use the Present Perfect Continuous to show that something started in the past and still continues now ( for 15 years).","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"The person who ________ in charge of a car is the conductor.","a":"is","b":"are","c":"was","d":"were","answer":"1","explain":"- The subject: the person + singular verb","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}